question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "In career mode of Need for Speed: Underground, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Metal Gear Solid V: The Phantom Pain runs on the Fox Engine.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "The first PlayStation console was released in the USA on December 3rd, 1994.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;League of Legends&quot;, there exists four different types of Dragon.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The character that would eventually become Dr. Eggman was considered for the role of Sega&#039;s new flagship mascot before Sonic was.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "TF2: The Medic will be credited for an assist if he heals a Spy that successfully saps a building.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named &quot;Atlas&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; takes place on Shadow Moses Island.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
